<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">BusyBox Free</string>
    <string name="busybox">BusyBox</string>
    <string name="version">v8.0</string>
    <string name="initialChecks">Loading..</string>
    <string name="noroot2">The "su" binary was not found on your phone. This application will not work without root.
    </string>
    <string name="sdcard">Failure! There is either not enough space on your SDcard or your SDcard is mounted! \n\n Check
        that your SDcard is not mounted and that you have at least 1.6mb of free space available then try again.
    </string>
    <string name="status">Status:</string>
    <string name="failed">It looks like the installation of BusyBox was not successful. \n\n Try installing to a
        different location, that may resolve the issue.
    </string>
    <string name="waiting">Waiting...</string>
    <string name="lookingbusybox">Looking for BusyBox...</string>
    <string name="lookingroot">Looking for Root...</string>
    <string name="rootfound">Phone is rooted.</string>
    <string name="accessUndetermined">I could not determine whether or not you have given Busybox root access. This
        application will NOT work if we do not have root access!
    </string>
    <string name="noAccess">BusyBox Installer was not allowed root access! \n\n This may be an issue with Superuser,
        open Superuser and make sure that you are allowing us root access. \n\n This application will not work without
        root access.
    </string>
    <string name="mounted">is currently mounted as RW.</string>
    <string name="failedmount">could not be mounted as RW, the install may fail.</string>
    <string name="pleaseMount">Before hitting the install button, please make sure you have remounted the /system
        partition of your phone to RW Access. Do not continue until after you complete this.
    </string>
    <string name="morethanone">More than one copy of BusyBox was found.</string>
    <string name="toolow">Not enough space to install busybox, we need at least 1600kb free \n\n Try removing some
        things to free up some space or try a different installation path.
    </string>
    <string name="select">Select where you want to install BusyBox \n All other copies of BusyBox will be removed.
    </string>
    <string name="applet">Applet:</string>
    <string name="custompath">Custom Path</string>

    <string name="whatisthis">This feature will allow you to see all of the applets that are included with my versions
        of Busybox from 1.18.5 on up. \n\n
        This feature will also allow you to check each applet, find out if it is installed, where it is installed, and
        the usage for the applet if it is installed. \n\n
        If you have an application which needs a specific applet and it is NOT here, please email me at
        StericDroid@gmail.com with the applet name and I will get it included ASAP.
    </string>
    <string name="foundhere">Found at:</string>

    <!-- main view -->
    <string name="currentstatus">BusyBox is</string>
    <string name="installed">Installed</string>
    <string name="not">not</string>
    <string name="notfound">BusyBox is not currently installed on your device.</string>
    <string name="busyboxversion">Current BusyBox version is</string>
    <string name="foundit">is installed.</string>
    <string name="installedto">BusyBox is installed to</string>
    <string name="installto">BusyBox will be installed to</string>
    <string name="installversion">Busybox Version</string>
    <string name="willinstall">will be installed to</string>
    <string name="amount">Free space in</string>

    <string name="installing">Installing Busybox... \n\n</string>

    <!-- AFTER INSTALL -->
    <string name="installedunique">It looks like the installation of BusyBox was successful! Congratulations! \n\n
        Keep in mind that by keeping this installed you will be notified whenever a new version of BusyBox is ready to
        be installed.
    </string>
    <string name="installedsomethingelse">It looks like BusyBox is installed, but It does not appear to be the version
        that you selected to have installed, you may want to try the installation again but this time using a different
        installation location.
    </string>

    <!-- First View -->
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="install">Install</string>
    <string name="restore">Restore</string>
    <string name="uninstall">Uninstall</string>
    <string name="utilProblem">I am unable to verify whether or not certain utilities needed for this application to run
        are present and functional on your device \n\n.
        This problem could be cause by a device that is not properly rooted or by superuser settings that are
        misconfigured. Please try the install again.
    </string>

    <!-- Tune View -->
    <string name="chooseSymlinks">Applets that are not checked will not be symlinked. \n
        (This is an advanced option)
    </string>
    <string name="notFound">Applet is not currently symlinked/installed.</string>
    <string name="symlinked">Applet is symlinked/installed.</string>
    <string name="hardlinked">Applet is hardlinked/installed.</string>
    <string name="cautionDoNot">Recommend NOT overwriting/installing this applet.</string>
    <string name="cautionDo">Recommend overwriting/installing this applet.</string>
    <string name="willSymlink">(Will symlink/overwrite/install)</string>
    <string name="willNotSymlink">(Will not symlink/overwrite/install)</string>
    <string name="symlinkedTo">Symlinked to:</string>
    <string name="notsymlinked">Not Symlinked</string>
    <string name="gathering">Gathering Information...</string>
    <string name="gatheringAbout">Gathering Information... \n\n processing:</string>
    <string name="noInfo">Information about this Applet could not be found.</string>
    <string name="longPress">Long press an applet for more info on that applet.</string>
    <string name="removeApplet">Will remove Applet/Symlink</string>
    <string name="leaveApplet">Will leave Applet/Symlink</string>

    <!-- BEFORE UNINSTALL -->
    <string name="beforeUninstall">Before hitting the uninstall button please consider that many root applications and
        custom roms require BusyBox to work, by uninstalling Busybox it could cause your rom and all of your root
        applications to stop working. \n\n

        This is an advanced option, and you should know how to reflash a rom, or repair your device in the event that
        removing Busybox does cause some undesired effect. \n\n

        Keep in mind that this will remove ALL symlinks which point to Busybox, This is an advanced option! \n\n

        DO NOT DO THIS UNLESS YOU KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU ARE DOING! I WILL NOT ANSWER EMAILS REGARDING THIS FEATURE, YOU
        HAVE BEEN WARNED!!!
    </string>
    <string name="uninstalling">Removing BusyBox... \n\n</string>

    <!-- AFTER UNINSTALL -->
    <string name="uninstallsuccess">It looks like the removal of BusyBox was successful! Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="uninstallfailed">It looks like the removal of BusyBox failed, either because we could not do so in a
        safe manner or because of some other technical problem. \n\n
        This may have left you with an non-useable system, which as stated before was one of the risks of removing
        BusyBox...you may need to reinstall your rom or do a system wipe to restore your device.
    </string>

    <!-- About -->

    <string name="about">BusyBox combines tiny versions of many common UNIX utilities into a single small executable. It
        provides replacements for most of the utilities you usually find in GNU fileutils, shellutils, etc. The
        utilities in BusyBox generally have fewer options than their full-featured GNU cousins; however, the options
        that are included provide the expected functionality and behave very much like their GNU counterparts. BusyBox
        provides a fairly complete environment for any small or embedded system.
        \n\n
        BusyBox has been written with size-optimization and limited resources in mind. It is also extremely modular so
        you can easily include or exclude commands (or features) at compile time. This makes it easy to customize your
        embedded systems. To create a working system, just add some device nodes in /dev, a few configuration files in
        /etc, and a Linux kernel.
        \n\n
        BusyBox is maintained by Denys Vlasenko, and licensed under the GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE version 2. (
        http://busybox.net/license.html )
        \n\n
        You can find more information about BusyBox here: http://busybox.net
        \n\n
        To be clear, I (Stephen Erickson) Did not write BusyBox, I wrote the installer and I compile each version of
        BusyBox for Android and hand select which applets are needed for Android, based on request usually.
        \n\n
        If you need an applet added, please email me at StericDroid@gmail.com
    </string>

    <string name="smart_install_loading">Smart Install is loading...You may go ahead and install Busybox or wait for Smart Install to finish loading.</string>
    <string name="advanced">To access the advanced features of Smart Install, touch the arrow above.</string>

    <!-- welcome -->
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to Busybox! \n\n Busybox now supports devices with Intel processors! \n\n
        New feature to allow the installation of any version of
        Busybox! (Pro Only) \n\n Faster loading times. \n\n Ability to automatically update busybox. (Pro Only) \n\n
        Ability to install specific applets one by one and choosing how they are installed. (Pro Only) \n\n
        The pro version of this application can be found here:
        https://market.android.com/details?id=stericson.busybox.donate
    </string>
    <string name="welcome_sale">For a limited time only, Busybox Pro is on sale for $1.80 only instead of the regular $4.99 price! \n\n Thanks to everyone for being part of making this the most popular Busybox installer! \n\n The pro version of this application can be found here:
        https://market.android.com/details?id=stericson.busybox.donate
    </string>

    <!-- Dialog stuff -->
    <string name="careful">WHOA! Careful...</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="install_type">Install Type</string>
    <string name="normal_install">Normal Install</string>
    <string name="smart_install">Smart Install</string>
    <string name="install_type_content">Would you like to use Smart Install, which provides a more thorough install with
        some small risks as it does replace applets or normal install which is much faster and a safer install.
    </string>

    <string name="proonly">This feature, and many others to come, is only available in the pro version of Busybox. \n\n
        You can get the pro version here: \n https://market.android.com/details?id=stericson.busybox.donate
    </string>
    <string name="proonly_custom">This feature allows you to install any version of Busybox, not just the ones that I
        compile. With this feature you can install Busybox compiled against the NDK, uclib, older versions I have
        compiled or any other version you can find on the web. \n\n This feature is only available in the pro version of
        Busybox. \n\n You can get the pro version here: \n
        https://market.android.com/details?id=stericson.busybox.donate
    </string>

    <!-- Notices -->
    <string name="proonly_smartInstall">This feature will enable smart install which will allow you to customize the install behavior to your specific needs using the options in this list. \n\n
        This feature is only available in the pro version of Busybox. \n\n You can get the pro version here: \n
        https://market.android.com/details?id=stericson.busybox.donate</string>
    <string name="warnSmartInstall">Please be aware that using smart install is for advanced users only! \n\n Some binaries found on your system should NOT be
        replaced by Busybox and doing so can make your device perform in an undesireable manner. The only reason you
        should tweak the settings below is if you know exactly what you are doing or if you know how to reflash your rom
        to fix issues that may occur from modifying the selections below.
    </string>

    <!-- Errors -->
    <string name="device_unsupported">Unrecognized device architecture. This should be an easy fix for me to make, please email me at StericDroid@gmail.com with your device information and the following information: </string>
    <string name="shell_error">There was a problem opening a shell with root access. This is either being caused by
        superuser/supersu or by a device that is inproperly rooted. \n\n Try removing superuser/supersu permissions,
        uninstalling this application, reinstalling this application, and then regranting superuser/supersu permissions
        for this application. \n\n You can check your device to see if it is properly rooted by downloading RootChecker
        from the Android market.
    </string>
    <string name="unexpectederror">An unexpected error has occured, please take a screenshot of the application and send
        it to me at StericDroid@gmail.com
    </string>
    <string name="fatal_error">An error occured while trying to install Busybox, try restarting the application and try
        again or you can email me, StericDroid@gmail.com, about the problem.
    </string>
    <string name="binary_verification_failed_install">We could not verify the integrity of the binary selected to be
        installed and as a result installation will not occur for the safety of your device. Please close the application and
        reopen it in order to re-attempt installation. If the issue persists, please email me at StericDroid@gmail.com so I can assist you with fixing this issue.
    </string>


    <!-- pro info -->
    <string name="autoupdate">The auto update feature automatically updates Busybox when a new version is available
        without any interaction from you. \n\n Currently only the pro version of this app has this feature. \n\n The pro
        version of this application can be found here: https://market.android.com/details?id=stericson.busybox.donate
    </string>
    <string name="replaceall">The replace all feature tells the installation to replace all applets, both those
        currently symlinked and hardlinked, with symlinks to Busybox. \n\n Currently only the pro version of this app
        has this feature. \n\n The pro version of this application can be found here:
        https://market.android.com/details?id=stericson.busybox.donate
    </string>
    <string name="cleanall">This feature will instruct the installer to make sure that applets are not duplicated after
        the install. This will keep your system cleaner, save more space, and will ensure that other applications do not
        have problems using the applets provided by Busybox. \n\n Currently only the pro version of this app has this
        feature. \n\n The pro version of this application can be found here:
        https://market.android.com/details?id=stericson.busybox.donate
    </string>

</resources>